How big do you think the anti-Zionist Jewish population is?
How big a problem do you think it is for us?
So I think two things can be true at the same time.
So I think small population, big problem.
It's me, your biggest problem.
You hard-boiled egg.
Isn't this you defending a Nazi salute from Elon Musk?
The head of the ADL, don't you oversee that training program
where police officers from the United States go over to occupied Palestine
and then bring those tactics back?
It's called the Deadly Exchange.
Aren't you the same ADL with a history of anti-blackness?
Who up until very recently had a cozy relationship with the FBI?
So you may want to take a step outside of one of those synagogues
selling stolen land in Palestine
and get a general temperature check from the rest of the world.
Nobody believes you anymore.
He goes on to cite a bunch of outdated statistics
about how much people love the pedophile settler colony,
but I have a few stats of my own.
Nearly 9 out of 10 Israelis say that there are no innocents in Palestine
and they support the mass murder.
61% of male Israelis do not see forced sex as rape.
100% of Thai foreign workers were sexually assaulted when working in Israel.
And we've known from Palestinians for years that they are being raped in the death camp,
some of them to death.
You have members of your government arguing that rape is a valid torture tactic.
And then you guys did a media tour with the rapists.
And before the false smears of anti-Semitism come in,
roll the footage.
People here are called anti-Semitic.
What is your response to that as an Israeli judge?
Well, it's a trick.
We always use it.
When from Europe somebody is criticizing Israel,
then we bring up the Holocaust.
When in this country people are criticizing Israel,
then they are anti-Semitic.